The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal
Subtitles by Bonobosubs
https://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Commander-in-chief Tian
always said this competition was a child's play
and not worth watching.
So why
have you come here today ?
Commander-in-chief De
Rank 500 000 Demonic Energy
(Late stage Ascendant)
Commander-in-chief Tian
Rank 600 000 Demonic Energy
(Peak Late stage Ascendant)
The Demon Emperor ordered me
to supervise this event.
The Demon Emperor ?
The Demon Emperor ordered
to change the rules of this second round.
Please welcome
the War Demon Drum !
the War Demon Drum ?
Oh my god !
What a spectacle !
How can we compete with this ?
This is my first time seeing it too.
This holy artifact can only be rang by a Commander-in-chief !
Such a powerful demonic energy !
Silence !
The goal of this round is to strike the drum.
The score is calculated by adding the number of times a team rings the drum.
The top 10 will advance.
This drum
is made from Ancient Demon hide.
If you aren't strong enough,
you will suffer a backlash without even making a sound.
But if you can strike it,
3 strikes make you a powerhouse
and 6 strikes...
make you a peerless genius.
If I could try,
I might go for 6 strikes.
But now...
This drum should only be rung for a Commander-in-chief's promotion
but was brought out today ?
Could it be that there is a promising talent
among this group ?
Back then, the Commander-in-chief Tian struck it 15 times
and shook the world.
It truly was an unprecedented feat.
Demon General Yu Sen,
step forward.
Yu Sen
Demon General
To have cultivated the Dao of Slaughter to this level...
This guy is about to impress everyone !
Having it make a sound isn't surprising.
But the true challenge
is the backlash.
Soul Devouring Slaughter, first layer !
He actually failed !
This drum is incredibly powerful !
Demon General Yu Sen,
has struck the drum 4 times
but doesn't have a helper.
This War Demon Drum is extraordinary.
But aside from the demonic energy,
it seems to have some kind of will.
4 strikes ?
It seems these Demon Generals
are nothing special.
Is Vice Commander-in-chief Xuan still confident in this person ?
Then, in your esteemed opinion,
who will take the lead ?
Naturally, it's him.
Demon General Ming Luo,
5 strikes.
Demon General Jin Yuan,
6 strikes.
5 strikes
6 strikes
4 strikes
3 strikes
You scum who injured a Demon General...
I will make you pay for it sooner or later !
Demon General Mo Fei,
step forward.
The Slaughter God of the border !
He is rumored to be number one amongst Demon Generals.
The Fire Demon Country has a huge bounty on his head !
It's finally his turn.
I wonder how many strikes he can make.
He's about to strike !
So it's not that difficult after all.
He hasn't stopped !
He hasn't used his full strength
yet has already reached 6 strikes !
This one deserves to be a Vice Commander-in-chief.
His appearance
is exactly the same as that man in the prison.
8 strikes !
Mo Fei is indeed impressive !
He's worthy of being called the Slaughter God !
Spectacular !
Vice Commander-in-chief Xuan,
victory is already decided.
Why don't you admit defeat ?
Mo Fei is indeed strong
but he can't compare
to the man I chose !
What is so special about this person ?
Is Vice Commander-in-chief Xuan...
afraid of him ?
Helper,
3 strikes.
Demon General Mo Fei,
a total of 11 strikes.
11 strikes !
How could a single person
even hope to match that ?
Brother Wang,
we've lost
this second round.
You,
step forward.
Brat,
do you dare to make a bet with me ?
Speak.
I bet you
can't strike it 5 times.
If you win,
I will personally recommend you to the Demon Emperor
for a Demon General position.
If you lose,
you get the fuck out of Sky Demon City.
This kid must be scared !
With his strength,
will he dare to bet with Jin Wuxu ?
Vice Commander-in-chief Xuan,
are you sure you haven't misjudged him ?
I don't need your recommendation to the Demon Emperor.
If I win,
I want...
your hand.
Fine !
If you can strike it 5 times,
I won't just give you one hand
but both of my hands.
What ?!
5 strikes ?
Poor Mo Lihai...
He's about to lose face because of this guy.
That's some bold talk.
Indeed !
He even wants Jin Wuxu's hand !
Watch closely
as I strike it 5 times !
5 consecutive strikes !
How is that possible !?
If I hadn't underestimated him before,
I wouldn't be as injured as I am now.
I told you before
that my Junior Brother
is far stronger than you think.
That's 5 strikes.
You...
should fulfill our bet.
I said you couldn't strike it more than 5 times.
How could you have won
without surpassing that number ?
Didn't Jin Wuxu just go back on his word ?
Aren't you afraid of shaming the Sky Demon Country ?
Since that's the case,
I'll make you admit your defeat.
When I first struck the drum,
it seemed to resonate with the law of the heavens.
Maybe...
this drum contains a strand of Dao ?
I will recommend you to the Emperor !
I want your hand.
You...
You shouldn't push your luck !
I said that
I want your hand !
Heaven's Might !?
His words resonate with the law of the heavens !
You're just borrowing the drum's power !
If you have the skill,
strike it 15 times !
If you can do that,
I swear to the Sky Demon
that I'll cut off one of my arms for you !
The backlash after 8 strikes
is too strong for a Soul Transformation.
9 strikes ?
He has already reached his limit.
It's impossible for him to strike 15 times.
Now I understand...
This isn't a test
but an opportunity !
He abandoned his defense !?
What is Brother Wang trying to do ?
The law of the heavens
can either be accepted or defied.
The surface of this drum is no different.
Striking is accepting,
fighting the backlash is defying.
Using the Life Seals to resist the backlash
was a grave mistake.
He's using his body as the furnace
and the sound as the fire !
He is undergoing marrow cleansing !
Within the drum's sound,
lies a defiant will.
Resist it, and you're harmed.
Accept it,
and it can become your own.
He finally understood.
I didn't give you this opportunity in vain.
It seems
he's about to breakthrough.
Such a sorrowful sound...
My son,
no matter what you've done,
you must take care of yourself.
No !
No !!!
Only then
will we be at peace.
Father !
Mother !
Zhang Hu !
I'm sorry...
Widow Ceng Si
pays respect to Brother Wang.
Condolences.
I, Du Tian,
will now wipe my consciousness
and become a soul fragment of the Soul Flag !
I cultivated for centuries,
stained my hands with blood,
stepped on the path of slaughter.
Why couldn't I protect you...
Promise me you'll take care of yourself.
Don't go...
Mother !
Ah Dong...
I miss you so much...
I will never meet you again...
The drum's sound conveys feelings
to reach the Dao through sorrow !
This brat
can actually move the hearts and minds of everyone here !
Was he...
called Wang Lin ?
Ascendant ?
How is that possible !?
Cross this gate
to become Ascendant.
My centuries of sorrow
were entrusted to the drum
and scattered by the sound.
Once this sound ends,
my mind will be cleared.
Only when one's Dao is complete
can they become
Ascendant.
Senior...
Wan'er !
The 15th strike is right before him...
Why did he stop !?
He's just a step away from Ascendant.
Is he going to sabotage himself now !?
The path to Ascendant
requires severing emotions and sentiments.
This final drum strike
is the law of the heavens cleansing his heart.
If he strikes it,
he will forget his feelings.
If he stops...
his Dao Heart will be trapped forever.
Back then, to breakthrough,
I severed all emotions and sentiments.
Will he...
dare to walk a different path ?
Little guy...
What will you choose ?
Break free from wordly delusions,
sever all attachments.
Only then can you reach Ascendant.
Ascendant...
So this is what Ascendant is !
The law of the heavens really is merciless !
Abandoning all emotions and sentiments
is a way to flee.
To cultivate like this
is not my, Wang Lin's, Dao.
My Dao is...
defying !
Defying this law of the heavens !
I can throw away the sadness in my heart,
but this lingering determination within me
is not something the law of the heavens
can take away from me !
Merciless law of the heavens,
let me see how
you will stop me from reaching Ascendant !
How will you stop me from defying the heavens !?
“Ascendant is a lonely road… For those without any lingering feelings or attachments, then aside from having enough celestial spiritual energy and their domain fusing into their body, stepping into the Ascendant stage is extremely easy! Because it is so simple, they won’t have much growth in their future cultivation because their heart never experienced this kind of struggle! “However, for some people, there are lingering feelings in their heart. For these kinds of people, their domain breakthrough is a test and at the same time torture…”
[...]
“For my Dao heart to be complete, I have to wipe all the sadness from my heart, but is doing so… really worth it…” Li Muwan’s figure appeared before his eyes, and scenes of her flowed across his eyes.
“If the price for reaching the Ascendant stage really is to wipe away all the sadness in my heart, to erase Wan’er’s figure, am I still cultivating the Dao… Is this really my Dao… Wan’er’s life and death and her eternal slumber, if I were to forget all of that, she will have become my cultivation furnace in a way…”
“Although as a man, I can’t be a saint, I always have a clear conscience. The heavens are ruthless, and if I were to be ruthless as well, how is that defying the heavens? I would be going along with the heavens!
“Throwing away my feelings is the same as those cultivators that left the Demon General competition. This is a form of escape, and it is not my Dao!”
“My Dao it to defy, to defy and walk against the heavens. That is my Dao! Ancient cultivators deceived the heavens to cultivate. I finally understand the meaning of the word ‘deceived.’ But were they really deceiving the heavens? They were clearly running away. Although they were not going with the flow of the heavens, the destination was the same!”
I've been walking this path for endless years
just to catch a glimpse of your silhouette.
Is it the compass of fate
that wrote this outcome for us ?
The heavens want to erase your existence,
that's the obsession guiding me.
Is this the path to uncover
truths from falsehoods ?
In a world of murk and shadow,
only the flame of truth can light the way.
Look at them all,
being carried by the waves.
being drowned.
I don't want to believe in whoever decides fate,
I will let the world refine my soul.
So what if I become an Immortal and defy the heavens ?
I will fight.
I'll break through the abyss of despair
to finally learn who I really am.
My body is stained by the bloody color of slaughter,
I embrace this obsession.
I won't glance back at the wasteland I left behind.
Even if this suffering shatters my soul
and I'm reborn countless times in hell,
I'll still fight.
It's hard to avoid loneliness
when you are above everyone else.
Can a moth that has witnessed the flames of a Suzaku
be afraid of a firefly ?